弱いことが…
Wow!
こんなに悔しいなんて 思わなかった。 ゴン… お前が 「念」を使えない３０日間
You'll find footage of today's entire meeting—
the entire meeting—on the Hunter site, so tell everyone who wasn't present!
俺が　お前を守るよ どんなことをしても 何に代えても
Tell them they absolutely have to watch it!
自ら白旗を揚げて 降伏を申し出たコルトの願いは
I will announce the results of the fourth vote
for the election of the 13th chairman.
瀕死の女王を助けてほしい というものだった それを聞き入れた モラウとノヴは
Out of 661 Hunters, there were 642 valid votes
彼をネテロに引き合わせた
and 19 absentees.
わしじゃ 今すぐ　キメラアントの研究チームを
6) Ickshonpe — 26
7) Teradein — 21
8) Morel — 20
9) Saccho — 15
10) Biscuit — 14
11) Sanbica, Linne — 13
13) Loupe, Bushidora — 12
15) Cutie — 10
16) Ging — 8
17) Tsezguerra — 5
18) Knov, Kite, Gon — 4
21) Kanzai, 3 others — 3
25) Hanzo, 5 others — 2
28) Saiyu, 8 others — 1 The turnout was 97.1%. 4th Election for the 13th Chairman
1) Pariston — 258 (39%)
2) Cheadle — 57
3) Leorio — 55
4) Botobai — 31
5) Mizaistom — 27
こちらに派遣せよ。
As the conditions were not met,
the vote must be redone.
うむ　王が生まれた。 『梵林医大』の李博士に 連絡して 有能で生きのいい外科医と
Voter turnout for the most recent vote in
the 13th chairman election exceeded 95%.
人工臓器の専門家も 総動員するのじゃ。 うむ。 [TEL]
Which means that for the fifth vote, we will have a runoff with the top sixteen
candidates, so keep that in mind.
４時間後に出発するぞよ。 ハッ！
I will now introduce the top sixteen
candidates in the order of votes received.
わしらも できる限りのては尽くす。 コルト君。
Pariston Hill, a Triple Star Hunter. The current Association vice chairman, his motto is the promotion of
a kinder Hunter Association.
ふぅ…。 これを着るのも　最後かのう。
Leorio Paradinight, a rookie. A rising star after punching Ging, he's currently studying to become a doctor.
おい　あれって…。
Botobai Gigante, a Triple Star Hunter.
ええ　「心」Ｔシャツ。 会長が本気で戦う時だけ 身に着けるという勝負服。
Advisor to the Zodiacs, he was the closest to the chairman
in both reputation and reality. Mizaistom Nana, a Double Star Crime Hunter.
コルト君 お主も「念」が使えるそうだが…。
The conscience of the Zodiacs, his practical nature has earned the respect
of the anti-chairman faction. Ickshonpe Katocha, a Single Star Hacker Hunter.
王を間近に見た経験を踏まえて
Living in the digital world, he has
yet to cast any votes himself. Teradein Neutral, a Double Star Headhunter.
忌憚のない意見を 述べてくれたまえ。 どうかな？　わしと王と比べて。
Specializing in discovering talent,
he seeks to reform the Hunter Exam.
やはり　すげぇ
Morel Mackernasey, a Single Star Sea Hunter.
針で突き刺されてるみてぇな 研磨されたオーラ
After defeating the Ants,
will he jump to Triple Star? His focus is preparation for the
arrival of more alien species.
恐らく 王に触れることさえ できないだろう。
Saccho Kobayakawa, a Double
Star Counseling Hunter.
その前に殺される 直属護衛軍の誰かにな。
Counselor of the Zodiacs, he seeks to reform the Association
from behind the scenes.
ホッホッホッホッホッ。
Biscuit Krueger, a Double Star Gemstone Hunter.
そうか…　嬉しいのう。
The Association's mother figure... Sorry, older sister.
この年で挑戦者か。
More and more people want her to scold them.
血沸く　血沸く。
Sanbica Norton, a Single Star Virus Hunter.
モラウ　弟子達の結果が 出るのは　今日だったな？
The Association's doctor, she has asked that no one vote for her.
はい。
Linne Hors-d'oeuvre, a Double Star Gourmet Hunter.
勝ち残った者と 研究チームを連れて コルトと共に巣へ向かえ。
The oldest Association Hunter, it's been five years since anyone
has heard her speak.
会長は？　まさか　お１人で王と？ あっ　いやいや
Bushidora Ambitious, a Single Star Blacklist Hunter.
古い知人に会いに行くだけじゃよ。
The Association's disciplinary officer, he advocates amending the Ten Commandments.
きっちり払えよ　１００万。 分かってます。
Cutie Beauty, a Single Star Cutiful Hunter. Recognized as the leader of
the Vice Chairman's fan club. She seeks to create a cutiful Association.
何すか？　１００万って。 いいんだよ。 行こう。 ああ。
Ging Freecss, a Double Star
Archaeological Hunter. The vagabond of the Zodiacs.
逆に　他の隊から　こっちに残った 変わり者もいるがな。
Leorio's in third? That's incredible.
結果的には　もめることがなくて 好都合だったかもしれん。
You can go to hell!
うむ　だが私では これ以上の処置は無理だ。
And he has no problem using
his Nen in front of a crowd. You can go to hell! Looks like he's an Emitter.
期待し過ぎないで。
So do people dislike Gon's dad?
とにかく　人工臓器を 片っ端から着けて行くわよ。
That was a standing ovation.
俺の臓器は使えないか？ 血も全部使ってくれて構わない！
Wow! You'll find footage of today's entire meeting...
１世代違ったら キメラアントは別種の生きもの。
Master Illumi...
どれだけ造りが違うか 分かるでしょう？
Yes, at once.
気持だけもらっておくわ 全力を尽くすから祈ってて。
Please wait one moment.
奇跡的に 全ての臓器が機能するようにね。
Thanks to Gotoh, I can see it now...
祈るだけ…　それだけなのか 俺にできることは
However, he's wary of Alluka's power. Which makes sense, given that one wrong move
テレパシー 誰か…。 テレパシー 誰か　おるか…？
is all it takes for the entire family to die. But on the other hand,
he wishes to control Alluka's power.
テレパシー ハッ！ こなたに控えております！ テレパシー 何なりと　お申しつけください！
That dilemma shows in his decision to
lock her up in a room filled with toys.
どうした？ 信号ね。 うむ　女王は 我々のように話すことはしない。
That's why he had Tsubone and Amane,
his most trusted butlers, accompany us.
通訳してくれる？
If something happens, they can
take us back immediately.
何か救命のヒントが あるかもしれないわ。 テレパシー 息子は…。
And he hopes they'll glean some hint
to help him control Alluka.
テレパシー 私の息子は…　無事か？
Tsubone and Amane understand their role, and they're being very cautious.
テレパシー どこか　身切れた所など テレパシー なかったか？ 「なかったか？」。
Gotoh and Canary are being subtle, but they're on our side and helping us.
テレパシー 大変お元気で　今は… テレパシー 今は　護衛軍を連れ
And then, there's Illumi.
テレパシー 女王様の傷に効きそうな薬草を 探しに出掛けられました。 「出掛けられました」。
The moment his name was spoken,
Amane's tension spiked.
実際には 師団長を殺して食った後 新天地を求めて旅立った。
This means Amane and Tsubone, and Father and Grandpa by extension, disagree with Illumi.
王は… 奴は　女王様の身など あくたほども気にしてはいない。
I'd guess that Illumi's plans for Alluka are...
テレパシー では　王は無事なのですね？ テレパシー はい。
That was a fine play, Gotoh. You threw out his name to see Amane's reaction.
テレパシー あぁ　よかった…。 テレパシー ハッ！　いけない！ テレパシー すぐに　王を旅立たせなさい。
If Tsubone were here, she would have noticed Gotoh's reaction
when he answered the phone, and she'd have distracted me or signaled
Amane to shut off her emotions.
テレパシー 私などに かかずらっている時間は
This is an internal family struggle, an inner mission.
テレパシー ありません。 テレパシー あの子には　世界を統べる 可能性があるのだから…。
When family members differ
in opinion or objective, they're each encouraged to do things their
own way, rather than unite in the same goal.
テレパシー 早くに生まれ過ぎたから
This is a contest!
テレパシー とても心配だったのだけども… テレパシー 私は使命を 全うすることができた…。
Father and Grandpa want Alluka
near, so they can control her, and they don't want me hurt by her power. I want
テレパシー それだけで　十分です…。
and to set Alluka free.
テレパシー 何をおっしゃるのです！ 女王様は　我々の道しるべです！
And...
テレパシー あなたがいなければ 皆　迷い果ててしまいます！
Illumi wants to kill Alluka!
テレパシー 自分の体のことは
Is this Killua? Yeah.
テレパシー 自分が　一番よく分かっています。
You removed the needle, didn't you?
テレパシー 私はもう…　長くない。
Yeah. I feel a lot better.
テレパシー しかし　何の心残りも…
Then I won't have to hold back when I kill you. Kill?
テレパシー ありません。
Me?
テレパシー やめてください！ 頼む！　生きてくれ！
You can't kill family members
during an inner mission.
使ってくれ！　俺の体を！
Family is off limits.
やれ！　やってみなきゃ 分からないだろうが！
Hey, hey, Amane...
話を…　女王の話を ちゃんと聞いてあげなさい。
Isn't this part great?
テレパシー 最後に…
Why is this story so mysterious?
テレパシー 一つだけ　頼みがあります。
Is that what
テレパシー 名前を…　考えたの。
Father meant?
テレパシー あの子に…　王のため…　に…。
You shouldn't consider that thing
to be a member of the family.
名前？
They're all thinking
テレパシー 「メルエム」…。
the same thing!
テレパシー 「全てを照らす光」 という意味です…。
Fine... I'll beat you at your own game.
テレパシー 私…　の…　かわいい…　子…。
Then, let's begin.
前にも　何かあったのか？
If you two are more than a meter apart, Amane will capture Master Alluka, and Tsubone will take you home by force!
俺が…　俺が取り上げる。
That was excessive.
この子は　俺が守る。
For now. Okay.
絶対！ 今度こそ　必ず！
By the way, am I allowed to kill Killua?
チッ。
I will
モラウ？
I was kidding.
人は食わないって誓えるかい？
Is that all right?
もし　誓えないなら
Oh, damn.
どこか　俺の目の届かない所へ 消えてくれ。
Was that on purpose? Certainly not.
だが　もし誓うなら…。
If at all possible, I'd like Gon to live.
何人たりとも　あんた達には 指一本　触れさせねえ！ 俺の目が　黒いうちはな。
Having more toys is always more amusing.
ヘヘっ　ヘヘヘへ 何のことはねえや。
Well, only if it's possible. It's okay. Brother's got you.
師匠譲りだぜ　俺が甘いのはよう。
Keep your eyes closed and hold on tight. Uh-huh.
うがっ!!
If that doesn't include Alluka, you're all enemies. Godspeed! Speed of Lightning!
だから　もっと俺は強くなる！
It's me. The situation's changed.
戻って来たカイトを
We've been separated from Master Killua.
がっかりさせないように！
We'll need four vehicles now.
なんだ ちゃんと分かってるじゃないの。 出会いは あんたのほうが早いけど
We'll follow the same route. If Master Killua contacts you, follow his instructions, but avoid
any sensitive information.
カイトとの付き合いは 私達のほうが長いから。
Master Illumi is aware of our movements.
この山を越えても まだウジウジしてたら
One of the butlers or a family
member is helping him.
叩き降ろすとこだったわよ。
Be sure to stay alert.
「カイトは　きっと
Understood.
ここでだって　スクワットや 腕立てくらい　できるでしょ。
Ah...
うん　確かに！
You've grown, Master.
スピンはさ…。 ん？
If I hadn't known about that
technique beforehand, I wouldn't have had time to react.
何で　ハンターになりたいの？
He will become an excellent assassin.
お金がいるの。 莫大な借金　返すため。
Oh, dear. These days, it doesn't
take much for me to tear up.
「コクチハクチョウ」って 知ってる？
In that case, he won't let Master
Illumi get the better of him.
ううん。
I shouldn't say that.
ある鉱山周辺でしか 生息できない鳥なの。
But I find it difficult to like Master Illumi
それが　なぜなのか 理由が　まだ不明なの。
and Master Milluki, who resemble their mother. Now, then...
水なのか　食べものなのか 気候なのか。
Time to set aside personal emotion. If he breaks the rules, everything changes.
だから 丸ごと買ったのよ　鉱山一帯を。 まぁ　正しくいうと 今は跡地なんだけど。
I need to devise a way to subdue Master Killua, taking his speed into account.
ただの子供で　何ひとつ 持っていない私達の話を
Okay! We should be far enough
away to take a break.
真剣に聞いてくれた 初めての大人。 私とスティンの生まれ故郷なの
I'd like to use Speed of Lightning to keep going, but to be safe, I should save my
energy for getting into town.
そこ。
Brother?
朝日を背に飛び立つ風景。 それが　私とスティンの
If I were gone, would everyone get along better?
廃棄物処理の候補地に 挙げられたと知って　気づいたの。
Alluka.
その場所が どれだけ自分にとって大切か。
If...
カイトは　ひと言 「うらやましい」って言った。 彼には　故郷がないの。 「どこで生まれたか 知らないから」って。
I were the only person in the
world who really loved you, would you be sad?
こ…　これは！
A magician who wishes to stay anonymous.
俺は　スピードキングだ
You two
誰にも俺は　止められない！
shouldn't be trying to fight back.
ヒャッホ！
Just evade his attacks.
あの速さなら
Save your energy for the mission at hand.
ヂートゥは　もう 国境を越えてるだろうなぁ。
You should follow Master Killua.
まっ　俺は　ゆっくり探すぜ。 餌も雌も　たっぷりいる場所
I'll play with you.
自分だけの楽園をな
A power that lets you rapidly fire coins
with more power than bullets...
牛　豚　人　猪　熊 どれでもいいから わんさか　いるとこがいい
Your power is strong enough to explain why
you'd send your subordinates away.
何しろ俺様は 大食いキングだからな
My coins pack enough power that you
can't escape unscathed if they hit. He must have used his power.
そして　王は
Elastic Love
Bungee Gum
東ゴルトー共和国にいた
You've said too much. I hope you don't regret it, you hack magician!